http://www.danielstrading.com/legal-notices/privacy-policy/

Skip to primary navigation Skip to main content Skip to primary sidebar Skip to footerHome / Legal Notices / Privacy PolicyPlease review our Supplemental Privacy Policy for EU Residents.
Your Privacy is Our Priority
Daniels Trading is committed to safeguarding the personal information that you provide us. This Privacy Policy describes how we handle and protect personal information we collect about individuals, such as you, who apply for or receive our products and services. The provisions of this notice apply to former customers as well as our current customers.
Why and How We Collect Personal Information
When you apply for or maintain an account with Daniels Trading, we collect personal information about you for business purposes, such as evaluating your financial needs, processing your requests and transactions, informing you about products and services that may be of interest to you, and providing customer service. The personal information we collect about you includes:
Information you provide to us on applications and other forms, such as your name, address, date of birth, social security number, occupation, assets, and income;
Information about your transactions with us and with our affiliates;
Information we receive from consumer reporting agencies, such as your credit history and creditworthiness, and other entities not affiliated with Daniels Trading; and
Information you provide to us to verify your identity, such as a passport, or received from other entities not affiliated with Daniels Trading.
Cookies
We use cookies and web beacons (also known as action tags or single-pixel gifs), and other technologies (collectively, “cookies”) to provide us with data we can use to improve your experience and to know you better. Cookies are small text files sent from Web servers that may be stored on your computer. Cookies enable us to capture how you arrived at our site, when you return, which pages on our site you visit, and to recognize that you are already logged on when we receive a page request from your browser. We may link the information we store in cookies to personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. We will never share this information with any 3rd party. Cookies are readable only by us and do not contain any personal information nor do they contain account or password information. We cannot and will not gather information about other sites you may have visited.
We may share usage information about visitors to our websites with reputable advertising companies for the purpose of targeting our Internet banner advertisements. The information collected by the advertising company through the use of these pixel tags is not personally identifiable. We may also use 3rd party software to track and analyze usage and volume statistical information including page requests, form requests and click paths. The third party may use cookies to track behavior and may set cookies on behalf of Daniels Trading.
All web browsers have settings that allow you to block cookies. By visiting our website with your browser set to allow cookies, you consent to our use of cookies as described above. If you choose to block cookies you may use our services but some functions may not work as designed.
How We Protect Personal Information
We limit access to your personal information to those employees who need to know in order to conduct our business, service your account, and help you accomplish your financial objectives, such as providing you with a broad range of products and services. Our employees are required to maintain and protect the confidentiality of your personal information and must follow established procedures to do so. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information. We do not rent or sell your name or personal information to anyone.
Sharing Information With Our Affiliates
We may share personal information described above with our affiliates for business purposes, such as servicing customer accounts and informing customers about new products and services, and as permitted by applicable law. Our affiliates include any entity that controls us either directly or indirectly, any company related to us by common ownership or control, and companies controlled or owned by us. The information we share with affiliates for marketing purposes may include the information described above, such as name, address and Daniels Trading account information, but will not include other credit information, such as credit history appearing on a consumer credit report or net worth and income information appearing on applications for our products and services.
Disclosure to Non-Affiliated Third Parties
In order to support the financial products and services we provide to you, we may share the personal information described above with third-party service providers and joint marketers not affiliated with us, including:
financial service institutions (e.g., advisers, dealers, brokers, trust companies and banks) with whom we have joint marketing agreements, such as agreements to market financial services or products that we jointly offer, endorse or sponsor; and
companies under contract to perform services for us or on our behalf, such as vendors that prepare and mail statements and transaction confirmations or provide data processing, computer software maintenance and development, transaction processing and marketing services.
These companies acting on our behalf are required to keep your personal information confidential.
Also, we may disclose personal information with non-affiliated companies and regulatory authorities as permitted or required by applicable law. For example, we may disclose personal information to cooperate with regulatory authorities and law enforcement agencies to comply with subpoenas or other official requests, and as necessary to protect our rights or property. Except as described in this privacy policy, we will not use your personal information for any other purpose unless we describe how such information will be used at the time you disclose it to us or we obtain your permission to do so.
Accessing and Revisiting Your Personal Information
We endeavor to keep our customer files complete and accurate. We will give you reasonable access to the information we have about you. Most of this information is contained in account statements that you receive from us and applications that you submit to obtain our products and services. We encourage you to review this information and notify us if you believe any information should be corrected or updated. If you have a question or concern about your personal information or this privacy notice, please contact your Daniels Trading representative.
“Opt-out” of Promotional Communications
You may opt-out of promotional communications via the following methods:
Visit https://www.danielstrading.com/unsubscribe/ to unsubscribe from E-mail lists.
Send an email to: optout@danielstrading.com.
Send a letter to:
Daniels Trading – OPT-OUT
100 South Wacker Drive
Suite 1225
Chicago, IL 60606
Primary SidebarTips & Strategies
For decades now, traders’ exposure to interest rates has been confined to allocating some small percentage of retirement funds to some bond fund for some reason like diversification.
Small Stocks (SM75) futures have made new all-time highs 5 of the last 9 trading days (56%). For context, SM75 made new highs just 5% of days going back to 2017. The phenomenon known as “positive drift” dictates that stocks move higher more often than not.
Daniels Trading is nonpartisan and does not endorse political candidates. The purpose of this blog post is to provide objective, unbiased information on what we believe could happen in the markets depending on the outcome of the election or how the election may impact the markets. The content is not intended to convey a preference… Read more.
More Tips & Strategies
Are Energy Stocks Cool Again?Is It Time to Limit Your Exposure to U.S. Dollar Devaluation?Quantifying Stock Market SentimentsDay Trading Strategies to Reduce LossesHow Would a Biden Presidency Impact the Futures Markets?Top Tips for Futures Trading During the U.S. Election
Trustpilot
FooterSite Navigation
Frequently Asked Questions
About Us
Customer Reviews
Contact Us
Futures Blog
Open a Futures Trading Account
